One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I don't want them to see my face!
لا أريدهم أن يروا وجهي
If they do, they'll kill me!
سيقتلوني إن رأوا وجهي
Shut up!
اخرسي
They already know it's you.
إنهم يعرفون أنكِ خلف هذا
Those guys are obviously wreaking havoc using your ability!
هؤلاء الأوغاد يستغلون قدرتك ليعيثون فسادًا
Okay! This mirror is the linchpin for the allied forces to escape.
عظيم، هذه المرآة هي مفتاح خروج القوات المتحالفة
Once I complete this task, I'll get my heart back.
سأستعيد قلبي حالما أنجز هذه المهمة
And once I have it, I'll teach all of them a lesson!
وحينما يحدث ذلك، سألقنهم درسًا لن ينسوه
Hey, Mother
أيَا أمّي
How's everything going inside?
كيف تجري الأمور بالداخل؟
I'm not hearing any shrieks yet... What's Big Mom doing?
لم أسمع صراخ بيغ مام بعد، ما الذي يجري لها؟
Just as we planned...
...كما خططنا
The cake is busted... and the flock of Straw Hats are on the loose...
...تم إفساد الكعكة، ونُسخ قبعة القش في كل مكان
The portrait of Mother Carmel is broken, too...
وصورة الأم كارمل تحطمت أيضًا
So why isn't Big Mom shrieking?!
لِمَ لم تصرخ بيغ مام بعد؟
What's going on?!
ما الذي يجري؟
Luffy-san, listen to me!
لوفي-سان، اسمعني
Big Mom has experienced too many shocks in quick succession,
لقد مرّت بيغ مام بصدمات متتالية
so she doesn't know how to focus her anger.
وبالتالي هي عاجزة عن تركيز غضبها
Okay! I'll do it if you think it's best!
فهمت، إن كان هذا قولك، فسأجرّب
Leave it to me!
دع الأمر لي
Stop Straw Hat! Don't let him get close to Mama!
أوقفوا قبعة القش، لا تدعوه يقترب من ماما
Why are you getting in my way?!
لِمَ تعترض طريقي؟
Bege!
يا بيجي
Bege, you bastard...
بيجي، أيها الوغد
Go to hell, Katakuri!
فلتذهب للجحيم يا كاتاكوري
What are you doing, Gang Bege?!
ما الذي تفعله يا غانغ بيجي؟
I knew you'd betray us, Bege...
توقعت خيانتك يا بيجي
Brother Peros!
أخي بيروس
Hurry up and shoot them!
أطلق عليهم النار حالًا
Yeah, I know.
مفهوم
Goodness... The future-seeing man sure is busy...
بحق، مُبصر المستقبل يريد لكل شيء أن يحدث بسرعة
But in this one situation, I, too, can see the future.
ولكن بهذا الموقف، يمكنني رؤية المستقبل أيضًا
Trapped in my candy, you'll all die with pathetic looks on your faces.
موتكم وأنتم مقيّدون بحلواي وتعلوكم هذه الملامح المثيرة للشفقة
There can be no other outcome!
هذا هو المستقبل الذي أراه
If only we had our raid suits...
...لو كانت لدينا البذلات القتالية على الأقل
you would not have gotten away with this!
لما سمحنا لكم بفعل ما يحلو لكم
Raid?
بذلات؟
What's that? Is it some kind of weapon? Lick.
ما هذه؟ أهي نوع من الأسلحة-بيرورين؟
Whoa-whoa, why would you want to bring such a thing to your son's wedding?
لِمَ عساك تجلب شيئًا كهذا في حفل زفاف ابنك؟
Get out of there, Reiju!
اهربي يا ريجو
It's you again!
أنت مجددًا
Don't get in my way!
لا تعترض طريقي
Sanji...
سانجي
What is he doing? He's causing trouble...
ما الذي يفعله؟ يا له من مزعج
Sanji...
...سانجي
I underestimated your kindness.
لقد استهنت بطيبة قلبك
Even after everything we've done to you, you still won't abandon us.
لا يمكنك التخلي عنا رغم شناعتنا معك
I've always hated being a Vinsmoke
لطالما كرهتُ كوني فردًا من فينسموك
and have always been ashamed of it.
ولطالما شعرتُ بالخزي من ذلك
But...
...ولكن
when I saw you all grown up...
عندما رأيتك بعدما غدوت بالغًا
I felt relieved!
شعرت بالارتياح
Because I realized that we still had a conscience in our bloodline...
لأنني رأيت ضميرًا حيًّا بين سلالتنا
Thank you... Sanji!
شكرًا لك يا سانجي
Oh, no! Sanji's family is...
مصيبة، عائلة سانجي في مأزق
You bastard!
أيها الوغد
Pedro!
بيدرو
Don't touch it, Luffy! Go!
لا تلمسه يا لوفي، انطلق
Thanks!
المعذرة
Five Thousand Tile...
خمسة آلاف لكمة
Fist!
قرميدة
Bege!
بيجي
Drop dead, Katakuri!
فلتذهب للجحيم يا كاتاكوري
Oh no, you don't!
لن أسمح لك
Mama...
...ماما
Mama... No!
ماما... كلا
M...
...الـ
Mother...
...الأم
Mother!
الأم
Mama!
ماما
All right!
عظيم
Now, take care of the rest by yourselves.
والآن، حان وقت عملنا
Well, I guess they can't hear me.
لا أظنهم قادرون على سماعي
Mama got injured?!
ماما أصيبت؟
She's weakened!
أصبحت ضعيفة
Hey! Somebody stop Bege and his men!
ليوقف أحدكم بيجي ومن معه
Bege!
بيجي
How dare you betray us!
سحقًا لك، كيف تجرؤ على خيانتنا
Farewell, Big Mom!
وداعًا يا بيغ مام
Mother...
...الأم
Hey... Listen, Mother.
استمعي إليّ أيتها الأم
Nobody will listen to me.
لا أحد يستمع إليّ
Hey, Mother... Where did you go?
أخبريني أيتها الأم، أين ذهبتِ؟
Big Mom's tears...
...دموع بيغ مام
This story goes back 63 years, to Elbaf in the New World.
يعود سببها إلى قبل 63 عامًا في جزيرة إلباف بالعالم الجديد
The island home of the warriors of Elbaf, the most famous of all the giants.
هذا المكان حيث تعيش سلالة العمالقة الشهيرة؛ محاربي إلباف
Now, come on.
والآن، تفضلي
Charlotte Linlin (Human, Five Years Old)
شارلوت لينلين (بشرية عمرها 5 أعوام)
What is this place?
ما اسم هذا المكان؟
I'll tell you later. Hurry and come down from there, Linlin.
سأخبرك به لاحقًا، لذا انزلي بسرعة يا لينلين
Uh-huh!
حاضرة
Hey, hey.
أخبريني، أخبريني
Where are we? Are you going somewhere?
أين نحن؟ هل ستذهبان إلى مكان ما؟
Papa has a job to do nearby.
والدكِ لديه عمل بالقرب من هنا
Linlin, will you be a good girl and wait for us here?
لينلين، هل ستكونين فتاة مطيعة وتنتظرينا هنا؟
What?! I wanna come with you...
ماذا؟ أريد الذهاب معكما
If you're a good girl, you can eat all the candy in your backpack that you want!
إن كنتِ فتاة مطيعة يمكنكِ تناول جميع الحلوى التي في حقيبتك
That's right!
أجل، هذا صحيح
All of it?! Then, I'll wait, I'll wait!
جميعها؟ إذًا سأنتظر سأنتظر
I'll wait for you!
سأنتظركما
See you later!
إلى اللقاء
Hurry back!
عودا بسرعة
Linlin...
...لينلين
Don't cry yet.
لا تبكِ الآن
After all the damage she caused, we're lucky she's only being exiled.
بعد كل المتاعب التي تسببت بها، قرارنا بنبذها كان رحيمًا
She's just... too much for us to handle.
ليس بوسعنا التعامل معها
They say the Holy Mother lives here. She'll save Linlin.
إنّ الأم المقدسة تعيش هنا لذا لا بدّ أنها ستعتني بلينلين
Let's set off! We're in a dangerous area!
لنُبحر، هذه المنطقة خطرة
See you!
رافقتكم السلامة
Wow! Those are some big fish.
مذهل، يا لها من سمكة كبيرة
GROWL...
...دمدمة
This is weird. They're taking too long.
هذا غريب، لقد تأخرا للغاية
I'm getting hungry...
...أنا جائعة
Mama, Papa, where did you go?
ماما، بابا، أين ذهبتما؟
Why aren't you back yet?!
لماذا لم تعودا بعد؟
As for Elbaf,
بشأن إلباف
a century ago, it was home to giant warriors that were feared by the entire world.
كانت قبل 100 عام موطنًا للمحاربين العمالقة الذين دبّوا «الرعب في أنحاء العالم، وكان يطلق عليهم «قراصنة العمالقة المحاربون
They terrorized the entire world and burned down countless cities.
لقد أثاروا الدمار في البحر والبر وأحرقوا عددًا لا يحصى من المدن
However,
ولكن
when the Giant Warrior Pirates' two captains suddenly vanished...
ذات يوم، فقد طاقم العمالقة قبطانيهما فجأة
they passed into legend.
وأصبحوا محض أسطورة
Shortly afterward, several of the remaining members,
وبعدئذٍ، تهوّر العديد من أفراد الطاقم بسبب غياب قبطانيهم
wound up being captured by the Navy and sentenced to death.
إذ قبضت عليهم البحرية وكانوا على وشك أن يُعدموا
Kill them!
اقتلوهم
Please wait!
انتظروا من فضلكم
Stop the execution!
أوقفوا الإعدام رجاءً
Heaven seeks a peaceful understanding!
السماء تطلب الصُلح
Until the appearance of a wandering holy woman!
راهبة جميلة متجولة ظهرت فجأة
Her name was Sister Carmel.
تُدعى الأخت كارمل
Sister Carmel
الأخت كارمل
Heaven seeks what?! What nonsense are you talking about?!
السماء تطلب الصُلح؟ عمّ تتحدثين؟
Do you know how much terror they've caused–
...ألا تدركين مدى الرعب الذي تجرعه العالم منهم
An even greater reason for penance! Why can't you see that?
أليس هذا سببًا وجيهًا؟ لِمَ لا تفهم؟
If you kill those men,
إن قتلتموهم، سيحشد محاربو إلباف جيشًا لنيل انتقامهم من البشر
Forgive their crimes!
اغفروا خطاياهم
I will guide them!
...سأتولى قيادتهم
To a world where all races join hands
إلى عالمٍ تعيش فيه جميع الأجناس بمودّة
and laugh together!
ويتشاركون فيه الضحكات
In time, she became "Mother" Carmel, and founded an orphanage
أصبحت كارمل تُعرف بالأم بعد ذلك الموقف
On Elbaf, the homeland of the giants,
استقرت في جزيرة إلباف حيث يعيش العمالقة
she served as a diplomatic bridge to unite humanity and giants.
وعملت كحلقة وصل بين العمالقة والبشر
And then, 37 years later...
...وبعد 37 عامًا
It'll be okay, Linlin.
ستكونين بخير يا لينلين
Mother Carmel (80 Years Old) And the Children of the House of Lambs
الأم كارمل (عمرها 80 عام) وأطفال بيت الحملان
We can all live together in happiness until your parents come back!
لنعش معًا بسعادة لحين عودة والديك
They won't come back! You've been abandoned!
لن يعودا، لقد نبذاك
All of the children here are quite interesting.
جميع الأطفال هنا مميزون
Interesting enough for our parents to give us up!
مميزون لدرجة أنّ أهالينا نبذونا
You'll be friends in no time.
ستتأقلمين معهم سريعًا
Uh-huh! Thank you!
أجل، شكرًا لكِ
I'm starving!
أنا جائعة
You're huge! Are you a giant?
يا لضخامتك، هل أنتِ عملاقة؟
In that case, let's eat!
حسنًا، لنأكل إذًا
There was a prince chased out of his country after a coup...
كان هنالك أمير نُفي من بلاده في أعقاب انقلاب على الحكم
and impoverished children who nearly fell into slavery...
وطفل كاد أن يُستعبد بسبب الفقر
Problem children whose parents couldn't handle them...
يعيش هؤلاء الأطفال المشاكسين الذين عجزت عوائلهم السيطرة عليهم في قرية العمالقة
Hey, Mother!
أخبريني أيتها الأم
Is she new?
أهي جديدة؟
But most importantly of all, for Linlin, who was always bigger than everyone else,
الجدير بالذكر أن لينلين التي لطالما كانت أضخم من الآخرين
Elbaf was the first place
شعرت بالارتياح عند رؤيتها للمواطنين والمنازل وكل شيء آخر في إلباف يتناسب مع حجمها
This is great!
هذا مذهل
The Next Day...
اليوم التالي
Why did it happen? Why did it happen?
هذا غريب، هذا غريب
Oh, no. What's the matter, Linlin?
ما الخطب يا لينلين؟
Mother, listen...
...أيتها الأم، انظري
A bear and a wolf were fighting in the forest.
الدب-سان والذئب-سان كانا يتقاتلان في الغابة
I wanted them to be friends because fighting is bad,
أردتهما أن يكونا صديقين بما أنّ القتال أمر سيئ
so I put them in the same cage yesterday.
لذا وضعتهما بالأمس في قفص واحد
But then Bear-san ate Wolf-san !
لكن الدب-سان قد التهم الذئب-سان
That's why I hit Bear-san.
ولهذا السبب ضربت الدب-سان
Bear-san looks sorry now. How many times did you hit him?
يبدو أنّ الدب-سان في حالة يُرثى لها، كم مرة ضربتِه؟
Just once...
مرة واحدة
Instant... death?!
قتلته بضربة واحدة؟
Oh, I understand!
هكذا إذًا
You just wanted them to be friends!
كل ما أردتهِ هو أن يصبحا صديقان
Linlin, you're such a sweet girl!
إنكِ لطيفة للغاية يا لينلين
Uh-huh!
أجل
Then, let's go play with everyone else!
دعينا نذهب للعب مع الآخرين
To Linlin, Carmel was the first person ever to really understand her.
بالنسبة للينلين، كانت كارمل الشخص الوحيد الذي يتفهم تصرفاتها
I saw it! Linlin killed a bear with a single hit!
رأيتُ لينلين تقتل دبًّا بضربة واحدة
She's dangerous!
إنها خطرة
Did you hear that she injured Eiri-kun, the giant?
هل سمعتم بأنها أصابت العملاق إيري-كن؟
She was only smacking him to hit a mosquito!
كانت تحاول ضرب البعوضة التي عليه
She broke lots of his bones!
لقد كسرت العديد من عظامه
Ouch! Ouch!
مؤلم
What are you doing, Linlin?
ما الذي تفعلينه يا لينلين؟
What?
ماذا؟
Mother! Help!
أنقذيني أيتها الأم
Well, he has an extra joint, so I was gonna rip it off for him.
لديه العديد من المفاصل في مرفقيه لذا فكرت بمساعدته عبر تمزيقها له
No, he's a longarm! It's normal for them!
كلا، هذه طبيعة جسده، إنه من قبيلة الأذرع الطويلة
Oh... I see...
هكذا إذًا
Ouch!
مؤلم
Linlin, what are you doing?!
لينلين، ما الذي تفعلينه؟
He has fins, so I was gonna rip them off for him.
لديه زعانف، لذا فكرت بمساعدته عبر تمزيقها له
Don't do that. Fishmen have the physical traits of fish.
توقفي، من الطبيعي أن يتمتع بمزايا الأسماك لأنه برمائي
Oh... I see...
هكذا إذًا
I was terrified!
كان ذلك مخيفًا
Everyone, forgive her!
سامحوها جميعًا
Linlin is a kind girl!
إنّ لينلين فتاة طيبة
Carmel forgave everything.
كانت كارمل تسامحها على كل شيء
Wait, wait!
انتظروا، انتظروا
No!
كلا
Linlin's gonna kill us!
لينلين ستقتلنا
Wait, wait! Wait, wait!
انتظروا، انتظروا، انتظروا، انتظروا
Ten months later in Elbaf, the Land of War, in the New World,
بعد 10 أشهر في أرض الحروب إلباف في العالم الجديد
Kashi
كاشي
the mighty warriors welcomed Linlin with open arms.
تقبّل الأقوياء منهم لينلين برحابة صدر
Oimo
أويمو
Wait, wait!
انتظروا، انتظروا
It's almost been 40 years...
...مضت 40 سنة تقريبًا
Have you ever seen a duel last this long?
أسبق وأن رأيتم نزالًا يدوم فترة طويلة كهذه؟
Oimo agrees! Let's go get them in 10 years!
أويمو يوافقك، لنذهب لإحضارهما بعد عقدٍ آخر أو نحو ذلك
Hey, Linlin! Did you guys finish preparing?
بالمناسبة يا لينلين، هل انتهيتم من التجهيزات؟
Kashi, preparing for what?
أي تجهيزات يا كاشي؟
Oh, Linlin-chan, I guess it's your first time.
أظن أنّ هذه مرتك الأولى يا لينلين-تشان
Before the Winter Solstice Festival, Elbaf fasts for 12 days!
نصوم في إلباف 12 يومًا قبل مهرجان انقلاب الشمس الشتوي
A fast?
صوم؟
We won't be eating anything. We're only allowed to drink water.
لن نأكل شيئًا باستثناء شرب الماء
That's 12 days starting tomorrow!
لمدة 12 يوم بدءًا من الغد
I'm gonna be hungry!
سأتضور جوعًا
But if you can endure it, we'll have a festival!
ولكن بعدما ننتهي سنحظى بمهرجان
Your true opponent is yourself, Hajrudin!
كافح نفسك يا هايرودين
Stand up, Hajrudin!
انهض يا هايرودين
Hajrudin
هايرودين
This giant boy, Hajrudin...
...هذا العملاق اليافع هايرودين
will eventually meet Luffy on Dressrosa, and be impressed by his determination.
سيلتقي لاحقًا لوفي في دريسروزا ويُعجب بعزيمته وإرادته
Along with Bartolomeo and the others,
وسيحتسي هو وبارتولوميو والآخرين الساكي مع لوفي لتشكيل رابطة الأب والأبناء
He is now a member of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet.
إنه حاليًّا عضو في أسطول قبعة القش
The tough boy!
الفتى القوي
Either Chief Dorry or Chief Brogy will return,
سيعود يومًا ما أحد الزعيمان دوري وبروغي
and the Giant Warrior Pirates will be reformed!
وحتمًا سيعود طاقم قراصنة العمالقة إلى البحر مجددًا
You're a warrior!
أنت محارب، إيّاك أن تتوقف عن التدريب يا هايرودين
Yeah!
أجل
I like that spirit, Raideen!
هذه هي الروح المطلوبة يا رايدين
"Mountain Beard" Jarl (345 Years Old) "Waterfall Beard" Jorl (344 Years Old)
لحية الجبل» يارل» (عمره 345 عام)
Chief Waterfall Beard and Chief Mountain Beard!
لحية الشلال-ساما، لحية الجبل-ساما
Carmel's ideas about trade over plunder
نصحتنا كارمل بالتجارة عوضًا عن السرقة، وهذا أمر جيد بالطبع
But we must not forget the fact that we are warriors!
لكن يجب ألّا ننسى هويتنا كسلالة محاربة
Yes!
أجل
The chiefs Jarl and Jorl are so cool!
يارل-ساما ويورل-ساما رائعان للغاية
Former Co-Captains of the Giant Warrior Pirates (Two of the World's Oldest Warriors) Heroes of the Giants
القبطانان السابقان لطاقم قراصنة العمالقة (اثنان من أكبر محاربي العالم عُمرًا) بطلا العمالقة
The most respected warriors of giantkind!
كما هو متوقع من المحاربين اللذان يحظيان باحترام جميع العمالقة
I wanna be like them some day!
أريد أن أصبح مثلهما يومًا ما
What are you two doing here today?
ما الذي أتى بكما إلى هنا؟
We're here to eat semlor in the village. We've come to call on the children from the House of Lambs. "(sing.)semla/(pl.)semlor" - traditional Swedish sweet roll
أتينا لاصطحاب أطفال بيت الحملان إلى القرية لتناول السيملا
It's good to see you, Linlin.
وصلنا في الوقت المناسب يا لينلين
What're Semlor ?
ما هي السيملا؟
They're sweet, delicious treats!
إنها حلوى لذيذة للغاية
What?! Sweets?
ماذا؟ لذيذة؟
Eating semlor before the fast will give us lots of nutrients!
ستزودنا السيملا بالتغذية اللازمة قبل بدء الصيام
Are we gonna eat them now? The sweets?!
هل سنأكل تلك الحلوى اللذيذة الآن؟
Sweet cream dolloped in sweet bread with marzipan,
كريمة حلوة مضافة إلى خبز حلو مع مرصبان ومنثور على قمتها بعض السكر
It's the fun before the fast!
إنها المتعة قبل الصيام
Sounds delicious!
تبدو لذيذة
All right, everyone!
والآن أيها السادة
We celebrate the recent birth of Prince Loki at the castle. And...
من أجل ولادة الأمير لوكي مؤخرًا في القلعة
the births of Road and Goldberg in the village!
ورود وغولدبيرغ اللذان ولدا في القرية
We thank the sun for their growth!
لنشكر الشمس على نمو أطفالنا
Thank the sun!
شكرًا للشمس
Thank you for the food!
شكرًا على الطعام
Yeah! Semlor !
إنها سيملا
There's plenty for everyone!
أعددنا الكثير، لذا كلوا قدر ما شئتم
So sweet!
حلوة
It's delicious!
لذيذة
I'm happy!
أنا سعيدة
Delicious! Delicious! Sweet! Sweet! Delicious! Delicious!
لذيذة، لذيذة، حلوة، حلوة، لذيذة، لذيذة
Delicious! Delicious! Delic–
...لذيذة، لذيـ
Whoa, wait! Hey, Linlin!
انتظري يا لينلين
Don't eat so fast! There won't be enough to go around!
لا تأكلي بسرعة وإلا لن يكفي للجميع
Don't forget to thank the sun!
لا تنسي شكر الشمس
Semlor !
سيملا
It's delicious! It's so delicious! Semlor !
لذيذة، إنّ السيملا لذيذة جدًّا
Day 3 of the Fast
اليوم الثالث من الصيام
Mother... I'm starving to death...
أيتها الأم، سأموت من الجوع
The Winter Solstice Festival celebrates the death and rebirth of the sun.
يُقام مهرجان الانقلاب الشتوي بمناسبة موت وبعث الشمس
After the harsh winter, the sun will shine down on us again.
ستكافح الشمس الشتاء القارس لتشرق علينا مجددًا
Day 4 of the Fast
اليوم الرابع من الصيام
The more we suffer, the more we will appreciate the sun.
كلما زادت معاناتنا، زاد تقديرنا وامتنانا للشمس
So... let's keep going!
لذا لنبذل قصارى جهدنا
If Mother says so, I'll... keep trying...
سأبذل جهدي إن كان هذا رأيكِ أيتها الأم
Day 5 of the Fast
اليوم الخامس من الصيام
I'm getting skinnier...
...بدأتُ أفقد وزني
You haven't changed.
لم تتغيري
Oh yeah? That's strange...
...هكذا إذًا، هذا غريب
Linlin!
لينلين
You're doing great! Just a little more to go!
إنكِ تبذلين حسنًا، لم يتبقّ سوى القليل
Uh-huh!
أجل
Linlin truly loved Mother.
ليلين أحبّت الأم من كل قلبها
Day 6 of the Fast
اليوم السادس من الصيام
The semlor were so delicious...
...كانت السيملا لذيذة جدًّا
I...
...أنا
want to have more.
أريد تناولها مجددًا
Day 7 of the Fast
اليوم السابع من الصيام
Oh, no!
مصيبة
Mother, help!
أيتها الأم، ساعدينا
What's the matter, Gerd?!
ما الخطب يا غيرد؟
Linlin-chan is...!
...لينلين-تشان قد
This is...
...هذا
Semlor !
سيملا
How could you...?
...ما الذي فعلتِه
Linlin!
يا لينلين؟
Bring me semlor...
احضروا لي السيملا
Semlor !
سيملا
Linlin destroyed the village of Elbaf!
دمرت لينلين قرية إلباف
It's a nightmare!
إنها شيطان
You've made a grave mistake, Linlin! You do not have the right to thank the sun!
ارتكبتِ خطأً فادحًا يا لينلين، أنتِ لا تستحقين شكر الشمس
Even a child can only be forgiven for so much!
لن نغفر لكِ هذا حتى لو كنتِ طفلة
Chief Jorl!
يورل-ساما
Semlor... Semlor...
...سيملا... سيملا
Carmel... I'm sorry...
سامحيني يا كارمل
She may look like a child...
...قد تبدو كطفلة
Don't do it, Chief Jorl!
توقف يا يورل-ساما
...but she's a demon!
لكنها الشيطان بعينه
Semlor...
...سيملا